https://www.royalpillow.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyWhat information does Royal pillow collect?Royal Pillow collect information from you when you place an order.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What does Royal pillow use your information for?Any of the information Royal Pillow collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: To process transactions – Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.How does Royal pillow protect your information?Royal Pillow implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an orderRoyal Pillow offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to? Royal Pillow keeps the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.Does Royal pillow uses cookies?Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain informationRoyal Pillow uses cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.Does Royal pillow discloses any information to outside parties?Royal Pillow does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. Royal Pillow may also release your information when Royal Pillow believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause Royal Pillow values your privacy Royal Pillow has taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. Royal Pillow therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page. Thank you for visiting Royal Pillow!Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceRoyal Pillow is in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), Royal Pillow does not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website click hereYour ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.Changes to Royal pillow Privacy PolicyIf Royal Pillow decided to change its privacy policy, Royal Pillow will post those changes on this page.Op-OutYou can Op-Out at any time from any future communication or promotions by either calling Royal Pillow at (305)634-3415 or by e-mail at sales@royalpillow.comContacting Royal pillowIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact Royal Pillow using the information below.Home2110 N.W. 23rd AVE. Miami, FL 33142 Dade sales@royalpillow.com (305) 634-3415 Scroll to top
